ifloor.com 2003-12-02

# iFLOOR.com - Privacy Statement

|   | The Internet's Flooring Store |  |   
---|---|---|---  
| DEPARTMENTS: | Carpet | Hardwood | Hand-Scraped Hardwood | Laminate | Bamboo | Cork | Blowouts | Wholesale |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| Leather | Rugs | VINYL TILE | LINOLEUM | TILE | MISC | SPECIALS | FIND A CONTRACTOR |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
**Code:** |   
| Privacy Statement

At iFLOOR.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.   
  
---  
**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
  
  * When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, shipping address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. 
  * When you sign up for one of our SALE NOTIFICATION SERVICES we need only an e-mail address--which we use to send the information you requested. 
  * When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 
  * We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about the merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store. 
  * We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new **i FLOOR.com** services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, visit the CUSTOMER INFORMATION PAGE to change your preferences. Make sure to change your preferences for each account or e-mail address you have left with us. 
  * When you send a quote or sample bag through the **i FLOOR.com** SHARE THE FLOOR service, we ask for your e-mail address and that of the recipient in order to complete your request. ifloor.com will never disclose or send promotional e-mail to recipient addresses provided only to the **i FLOOR.com** SHARE THE FLOOR service. 
  * For Purchase Circles, we group the items we send to particular ZIP and postal codes, and the items ordered from each domain name. We then aggregate this anonymous data and apply an algorithm that constructs bestseller lists of items that are more popular with each specific group than with the general population. None of the data is associated with any individual's name. 

**How does ifloor.com protect customer information?**  
  
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
  
**What about "cookies"?**  
  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies enable us to provide shopping features and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. 
  
**Will **i FLOOR.com** disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
  
**i FLOOR.com** does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to outside parties. We do share some customer information with our trusted partners for transactions that begin at a partner site. These are trusted parties who will not sell your information to outside sources. 

Also, **i FLOOR.com** may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**In summary:**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at **i FLOOR.com** possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to never@ifloor.com . If you never want to receive any announcements or special offers from us, visit the CUSTOMER INFORMATION PAGE to change your preferences. Remember to change your preferences for each of the e-mail accounts you have given us. 

**Your consent:**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by iFLOOR.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Tell us what you think!**

**i FLOOR.com** welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to feedback@ifloor.com.   
  
Foreign Accents is Casual  "Foreign Accents is positioning itself as the casual lifestyle people." Rug News, October 1999 

Comments about this page? Click here.  
| DEPARTMENTS: | Carpet | Hardwood | Hand-Scraped Hardwood | Laminate | Bamboo | Cork | Blowouts | Wholesale |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| Leather | Rugs | VINYL TILE | LINOLEUM | TILE | MISC | SPECIALS | FIND A CONTRACTOR |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
Shipping Info | Tax Info | Privacy Policy | Why buy flooring from iFLOOR? |  
Service Areas | [Area Rugs](http://www.arearugsonsale.com/) | [Commercial Flooring](http://www.trueflooring.com/) | Samples  
**If you are interested in becoming a new supplier, email our[Product Manager](mailto:newproducts@ifloor.com).**  
Flooring Headquarters: When you need floors fast, visit iFloor, the full service flooring store.  
©1999-2003 [iFLOOR.com](http://www.ifloor.com/sitemap.html)TM. All Rights Reserved.
